[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of the following card games is the Queen of Spades to be avoided?", "correct_answer": "Hearts", "incorrect_answers": ["Bridge", "Whist", "Spades"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Was Bernardo OReilly, played by Charles Bronson, one of the Banditos in The Magnificent Seven?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous NBA basketball star made an appearance as co-pilot Murdock in the movie Airplane!?", "correct_answer": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar", "incorrect_answers": ["Julius Irving", "Magic Johnson", "Kevin McHale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the best evidence of a properly brewed espresso shot?", "correct_answer": "its crema", "incorrect_answers": ["its aroma", "its clarity", "its color"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Tomato Frog is native to the eastern coast of Madagascar.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the family name of the heroine in the 1979 thriller Alien?", "correct_answer": "Ripley", "incorrect_answers": ["Rilley", "Radcliff", "Raleigh"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When burning fuel for energy, small particles are thrown into the air that are visible in the form of smoke.  It is called this type of pollution.", "correct_answer": "Black carbon pollution", "incorrect_answers": ["Outdoor pollution", "Water pollution", "Indoor pollution"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What design is depicted on the national flag of Switzerland?", "correct_answer": "Cross", "incorrect_answers": ["Sun", "Star", "Leaf"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Monty Pythons Life Brian was banned in Sweden.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which continents are entirely in the Western Hemisphere?", "correct_answer": "North America and South America", "incorrect_answers": ["North America, Europe, and Asia", "Europe, Asia, Africa, Australia", "Australia and Antarctica"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meat is used for the making of the traditional South African dish Tomato bredie?", "correct_answer": "Lamb", "incorrect_answers": ["Chicken", "None of these", "Pork"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fibromyalgia is most common in women.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]